Andrey Faigon Software Developer

GTA, ON | 647-870-2870 | andreyfaigon@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrey-faigon-full-stack-developer https://faigon.tech/

Summary

A solution-driven software developer with extensive experience creating web application and development of both the front end and back end as well as database expertise. My skills include, but are not limited to, being a team player, problem solver, independent learner, independent worker, and adept at time management.

Skills

Frontend	Backend	Database	UI
React.Js	Java	Microsoft SQL	Bootstrap
Angular	C#	MySQL	Next.Js
ASP.NET	JSON	MongoDB	Angular Materials
JavaScript ES6+	RESTfullAPI	Mongoose	CSS
HTML5	Node.Js	_	WordPress

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer

2022 - Current Grow Mushrooms Canada, Victoria, BC

- Created and managed a cross-platform application from conception to execution, designing the home page, the site layout, and the features
- Integrated data from various back-end services and databases
- Reviewed code, reported, debugged problems, and correct issues
- Developed landing pages, dashboards and online applications using HTML, CSS, and JQuery.
- Increased site traffic 30% by developing user-oriented visuals and features using front-end languages, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Collaborated with senior developers to ensure application integrity, optimal performance, and responsiveness

Software Developer

2020 - 2022

ISA Machinery Design, Burlington, ON

- Developed visually accurate user-driven websites from design using HTML / CSS / JavaScript and integration of customized plug-ins within content management system
- Applications developed with React. Design and development of interactive UI components and APIs
- Integrated new and existing software into new and existing machinery
- Debugged and tested software and it's implementations
- Participated in team meetings and provided updates on deadlines, designs, and improvements

Software Developer

2017 - 2020

Fiera Foods inc., Toronto, ON

- Created test framework using Selenium WebDriver for further tests creation
- Development of automated regression tests using Katalon Studio
- for web applications.
- Supported Portal Application using best software development practices
- Diagnosed and resolve technical problems
- Test documentation creation using QA best practices

Education and certificates

Diploma	2021- 2022	triOS College - Web Application Developer
Certificate	2019 -2020	Conestoga College - Java Developer
Certificate	2018 - 2019	Go2IT – Java EE
B. Sc	2008 - 2012	Bar-Ilan University - Biotechnology

Languages: English, Ukrainian, Hebrew

Hobbies: FPV (pilot certificate - RPAS)

References provided per request